George F. Aker Papers
George F. Aker Papers
- National Seminar on Adult Education Research
  - Annual meetings, 1961-1968; 8 folders (Box 7)
Thiede, Wilson B. - Florida State University / Correspondence 1963 Aug. 23 (box 2) 1963 Sep. 5 (box 5) 1963 Nov. 18 (box 2) 1967 Jan. 26 (box 5) 1967 Apr. 7 (box 5) 1967 Oct. 31 (box 5) 1968 Jun. 4 (box 2) 1968 Jun. 12 (box 5) 1968 Jul. 29 (box 2) 1969 Jan. 22 (box 5) 1969 May 22 (box 5) 1969 Jul. 14 (box 2) 1969 Aug. 6 (box 2) 1969 Aug. 12 (box 5) 1969 Sep. 19 (box 5) 1969 Oct. 10 (box 5) 1970 Aug. (box 5) 1970 Dec. 4 (box 5) 1970 Dec. 29 (box 2) 1971 Jan. 15 (box 5) 1972 Mar. 21 (box 3) 1972 Jun. 19 (box 3) 1972 Jun. 26 (box 5) 1977 Feb. 3 (box 4) 1977 Jun. 29 (box 5) 1983 Aug. 2 (box 4) 1983 Sep. 6 (box 4)